{
    "id": "b29755a73bbc43e88308518f2a212a50",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Thomas Alva Edison is one ………………….. the most famous inventors who ever lived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6c38a84cda5480898c8ede96c809a01"
        },
        {
            "question": "Edison, who is known as the Magician ………………. Menlo Park, accomplished many successes …………….. his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in, in",
                "of, of",
                "of, in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "86b7aa2141ba4ef890363f5120896cb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has 1093 patents ……………….. telegraphy, photography and electric lighting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c032b2761cf74721bc2948300d9d062e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some ……………… his inventions were original.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95259d9aaf1242ff955dc23e43c246f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some others were improvements of things invented …………….. others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e24bb8152e74d2e95c7dd43574d0f41"
        },
        {
            "question": "Edison also established a factory ……………… invent things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff7fd9f107244b06ad33cf4c0ba14f97"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thomas Alva Edison was born ……………… Ohio ..................... February 11,",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in, at",
                "at, in",
                "in, on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d3c5dd6788c546448c6b8b550922490e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He died ……………… October 18, 1931 …………….. New Jersey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in, in",
                "on, in",
                "on, on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1593e2793364430e995803fbf3cce8a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the seventh and last child …………….. his parents who had no special background.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c62325df4c764c0085798f02d9d26400"
        },
        {
            "question": "Edison started school …………….. seven.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f5bc3b32e964ded8070798e08fb7fff"
        },
        {
            "question": "After three months his mother pulled him …………. school and started teaching him herself ………….. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out, in",
                "out of, at",
                "out of, in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76f95309764c42e19d1cd4e63d1f8295"
        },
        {
            "question": "His parents encouraged him to learn things .................. his own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e002b8e1a28440848f22e784c568b57a"
        }
    ]
}